(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) You were made to be ruled.
In the end, it will be every man
for himself.
What do we do?
We get ready.
There was an idea to bring together a
group of remarkable people.
So when we needed them, they could fight
the battles that we never could.
Gentlemen, what are you prepared to do?
No offense, but I don't play well with
others.
Big man in a suit of armor.
Take that away, what are you?
A genius, billionaire, playboy, philanthropist.
If we can't protect the earth, you can
be damn sure we'll avenge it.
Dr. Banner, your work is unparalleled.
And I'm a huge fan of the way
you lose control and turn into an enormous
green rage monster.
Thanks.